Hello everyone, this is Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love!
Following the Equal Love Boat Race last time, what do you think?
What a surprise! Boat Race Hamanaka gave us English!
Thank you very much!
You know, I visited Boat Race Hamanaka last time, too.
We lost in a boat race.
But Miya won.
I lost.
Yes.
Meiya won.
So what?
Because of Meya?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
Also, Milinya's here today.
She's a little late.
But I'm sure she'll be here soon.
I'm going to do my best today, too.
At the last venue, this time you heard Manako's story.
Hey.
After that, we had a talk with you.
Yes, we did.
After that, we had a series of meetings.
Today, we're officially working.
What?
But we're doing it now.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for finally officially recognizing our boat racing team.
I didn't even mention the start at lasts today, so...
We'll be waiting for you at the Louvre, Antofri. Thank you.We are also waiting for the louver antfri Thank you!
Kan-naku-kun, long time no see! Long time no see!
Yes, it's been a long time.
Every time, right?
You've come a long way today with your brain gallery.
Thank you very much.
Even the staff gets paid to come here.
First, the cab fare to Shinagawa Station.
It started before.
I put it in the Japan Post Bank today, too.
We'll definitely get it back and take the green car home together.
Let's eat ice cream together!
Eat, eat, eat!
Let's eat ice cream on the bullet train!
Wow, that's so encouraging!
I'm really grateful that the director is here.
I'm working today.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Another one?
Yes, sir.
Are you sure?
Is it not good?
A former player?
Yuka Takahashi.
Yes, please.
Hello, hello.
I'm Yuka Takahashi.
I'm Yuka Takahashi.My name is Yuka Takahashi
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Isn't it amazing? Really.
A former racer.
This is what happens when you get to work.
That's great. That's great.
Please.
Thank you very much.
I've been a racer now until December. I've been a racer for a long time.
Lately.
I've been doing some forecasting on YouTube recently.
I've only been forecasting for a little over a year.
I'm still a rookie.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I've been hoping that I could teach you something.
Thank you very much.
So you're going to teach us directly today?
I've been doing this for a while now without any.
That's right.
Really maybe even boat racing fans.
Finally, we can watch without stress.
We've just been making a lot of noise.
I'm sorry for all the trouble we've caused.
I'm sorry.
Starting today, we're going to start teaching you.
Yes, starting today.
By the way, this boat racing club...
I know you've seen it.I heard that you saw it.
I saw the last time you were at Lake Hamana.
What did you think of that?
I don't know, but I think Lake Hamana is pretty easy to get to with the 13th.
Is that so?
I like that box.
If it's a boat race track for Millinia...
I see.
Yes, sir.
I want to win.
Yes, ma'am.
If you could just tell us what you know about us.
I thought I'd wave to you.
Thank you, sir.
By the way, once you're a successful boat racer.
Can I spend the money to buy one?
No, sir.
Yes!
I'm buying as much as I can.
I see.
That's really a credit card then.
Let's buy the same one.
No fair!
I'll buy the same one.
I'm sure we'll win today.
Oh, my gosh!
That's why we like each other's handwriting and everything.
Let's make it more D-self-portrait.
Oh, my God!Ah!
Just for today...
Hide yourself.
Make yourself smallest.
I'll copy everything.
I'll copy you.
The exhibition of the five races will start immediately.
I'd like to ask Mr. Takahashi a lot of questions
I would like to learn from you as soon as possible.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
In the first place, exhibition is something we always do.
Khan, you're so good, this guy!
He's so good!
We sometimes choose and do things like that.
But how do you see an exhibition?
How do you see an exhibition?
I think an exhibition should start with a start exhibit.
The start of the exhibition is to check the legs of people who are stretching out from the slit.
or checking the legs of people who are stretching out from the slit.
When you wake up the boat...
or a person who looks slimy and heavy
and so on.
That also affects the real race.
That's right.
Even in the race, if you're stretched out...
Or if they look a little heavy...
I think it's important to check.
I think it's important.
Also, I think it's important to do the rounds of the exhibition.And then there's the lapsed exhibit.
I think there are six of them going around in order.
One of them in particular.
I think it's too much of a hump mark.
who have a great sense of acceleration at the exit.
I'm not sure.
I was comparing them with the other six.
I think you can see that this person might be fast
I think you can tell by looking at them that this person might be fast.
I think you should check that person out.
Does he/she seem to have good legs?
He seems to have good legs.
I can use that as a reference.
But the players also have to give 100%.
It's not on the exhibition.
I see.
Why is that?
If it capsizes...
I'd be sidelined.
I'm adding or subtracting 60% or 70%.
I'm only adding or subtracting 60% or 70%.
so I only refer to the good ones.
As for me
By the way, as a player
I was on the side of being predicted.
At that time
Takahashi-san, did you have the right idea today?
Was it right?
But I really thought
I'm fine with the exhibition just as long as it doesn't topple over.The exhibit was like OK just don't capsize.
I was riding so
I was trying to make a good turn and the turn
I wasn't trying to make a good turn.
I was just trying to get a feel for the good parts.
and don't trust it that much.
That's right.
Oh, no.
We were listening to the sound.
Right.
It's so embarrassing.
You only nibbled on the top.
Embarrassing.
It's the start timing, right?
Yeah.
Everyone does that.
I think it's the best.
The key is to add or subtract from the starting Braille timing, so that if you're flying a little bit, you can get a good start.
For example, if you are flying a little bit, and you lower your center of gravity, you can get a good start of about 15 tenths, so I think it's no good because you are flying.
For example, if you are flying a little bit and you lower your center of gravity, you can get a good start of about 15 tenths.
So I don't think I'll be able to decide if I have a good start or not based on that timing alone.
I'm starting to think it's better to die, and I want to see it in action.
I think the time around the foot and the time for one lap will be displayed, and if the time is good, the person who is red or yellow will be over there.
Yes.
The early foot is the foot that has the tan mark, the foot that's turning, the foot that's going around, the foot that's going around.
The foot that is coming out or the foot that is extending is the foot that is coming out when the steering wheel is turned and the lever is depressed and the foot comes up.
If the extension foot is good, it will come out like this even if you are running together.
So, since we are amateurs, we shouldn't think we know what we're talking about.
I think you are a bit too light and don't understand the time by yourself.
So, Winyan holy Ist! That's right, Winyan, holy Ist!
The director, Até 沒沒, is here today to show us the beauty of the one-step steer.
I'm sorry.
I'm sure you'll be happy to know that Miriya's birthday box is very easy to buy, so let's buy all of them today too.
I'm Mirinya from Amanako.
I'm Mirinya from Amanako, and I'll be back again today.
I'm sure there will be someone who will go down to the pit again.
If that doesn't happen, we'll be fine.
You often say it's just like on display... how do you feel about it?
Do you feel that other boats are coming in as you expected or as you expected?
I think there are people who come to the front of the boat.
I think there are people who sometimes come to the front of the boat, and at that time they are like, "Oh, I've been robbed.
Then, sometimes, when they are clearly overtaking, they are already encouraging.
I'm thinking about whether or not I can resist.
But if it's with my seniors, I said I can't resist.
But I'm going to insist on it while keeping my course, regardless of my seniors.
So I've already decided in my mind whether I'm going to resist or not before that.
I'm not saying that's good or bad, it's just that I'm the one who doesn't have it.
The meaning of "Let's go with you, love" is changing more and more, even though it's written as it is.
The meaning of the song is changing rapidly even if it's included as it is.
It's the personality of the group.
It's about the same.
It's not so much, but I feel like number 4 peeks out from the slit a little bit.
What do you mean?
I saw that the board position was the starting position, and from there, only the 4th seemed to have grown a little bit.
So, I'm checking to see if there's a chance for a little stroke if he's going to extend from the 4th corner of the dash, if he's going to make the start.
The 4 is coming.
If it's a player who goes to the start and stretches out, I'm thinking that he might be able to get another shot at an easy tail.
Usually, one of them is hard, isn't it?
I think the other one isI think we have one more winner here.
Can I have a three-horse race?
Why not? Why not?
It's my best chance.
Except one.
Because the first boat is an A1 player.
That's right.
This race...
They say it's a lunchtime race, and there's an A-ball in one slot, and B-balls in all the other slots.
I don't know anything.
That's right.
The inside is strong here, and the plan is to win from the inside.
That's like rock-paper-scissors-scissors, "I'm going to make par," isn't it?
It's like rock-paper-scissors-scissors, "I'm going to make par, but what are you going to do about it?
That's right.
So you don't know if you're going to play rock-paper-scissors.
Yes.
If it collapses like this, it's already full.
It's a race that could happen.
Even if the winner runs away, I think it'll be a close race.
Any B-class players of note?
If Shibata didn't have a flying boat, I thought he would have been able to make a good run and I would have liked to get a good shot at him.
When we play, we don't really look at the flying boats that closely, but we just think that they have a flying boat, but is it scary for the players?
If you have one boat, for example, you still have to take time off after this race if you haven't used up your vacation days, but if you have another boat, you have to take two more months, which means you have three months off.
So you have to be very careful mentally.
Yes, I'm very careful.
I don't want to draw attention to myself.
In this case, the second and fourth boats are flying, so we'll have 135 boxes.
I knew it.
I knew it!I knew it.
It's possible.
Nori-san is the only one who won.
It's become a very deep show.
That's great!
To the funder!
How did you do it with only Nora Nori and only Nora gamblers?
The depth of the content...
You pulled it out all the way to the top.
I don't think so at all.
On the contrary, the words are getting thicker and thicker.
I see.
It's becoming more literal.
Hitomi's shallow knowledge is a little too much.
Miryan is good with 315.
That's what I'm doing today.
I'd like to buy 315, but I'll think about it when I can do it myself.
I'll buy with Hitomi's 13.
It's like a pincushion.
Because 13 won't hit.
Yes, I'll buy it.
I thought 13 was going to come.
That's right.
But it's still a double.
It's a double.
I don't know what to do.
One three in a row?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.Absolutely not!
He writes like Mr. Sasahara.
One, two, three...
What's with the "absolutely not"?
It's so good!
I'll make it 3 for 1, and it'll hit like crazy.
A1 player says, "I'll make par, I'll make par!
Wouldn't it be cool to buy all 3 ones?
I'm scared.
You can't do that, right? But when it comes, it'll be great.
He said, "The best is good.
That's right.
All three number 1s?
That's so cool!
It's against the theory to let other people do it.
I want to buy it until it's number one.
Everyone buys at number one.
The only reason why it's so expensive is because
It's more expensive to remove the first place.
For example, you could put the first place in the second place.
That's right.
It's possible.
I just read a comment from a player on the internet.
I read it.
I read the comment of the second boat.
She doesn't stretch out after turning.
And even after the start, she goes down.
The third boat doesn't feel like pushing after turning.
I'll think about maintenance.
I'm getting negative comments.I'm getting negative comments.
And even though the fourth boat was negative, there was a feeling that the start was going to be
It's just the way it stretches out.
Maybe the second place 3 is a little bit out of the mix, and we're going to
I think the 4th boat is going to come out and attack.
It's possible that the race will turn out like this.
That's possible.
By the way, the 5th one...
The straight line is a little bad, but the start and the end are good.
Number 6 is good around the slit.
And his start is above average.
If number 4 goes on the offensive...
I wonder if No. 5 and No. 6 have enough legs to keep up with it.
Wait a minute.
The starting exhibit also excluded a little slit.
I think it's the engine of the way to stretch.
I think that's the engine of the growth.
Here we go.
Wow!
She's the first boat, isn't she?
The first boat.
The first and second ones with some color on them.
That's good.
It's the fourth.
No. 4, but we've only got the exhibition time and the straight line time.
So it's not colored.
Maybe number 3.
The reporter's prediction.
Reporter's guess: 1, 3, 6.Reporters are going one, three, six.
One, three, six.
Is it right? This.
Why?
Even the reporter in charge is suspicious.
I've got an image of Mr. Arata in boat No. 6.
When it's a crowded race like this.
Yeah...
That's it!
1, 2, 3 4 and here's the turn.
One, four two, three and one, four, six.
Ew.
Yeah.
I'd do it this way.
It's getting harder.
But I'm going to go with one.
I want to believe in the escape.
Then I believe with you.
The director bought early.
He's already moved on to the Naruto class race.
Wow!
Oh, no.
Simultaneous?
Simultaneously.
Wow.
I've been thinking lately... if you take a hit on the first one...
I have to spend more to get it back.
That's true.
It's a relief.
I've finally learned that it's better to be conservative with the first shot.I finally learned recently that it's better to be conservative the first time.
I've been trying so hard to get it back that I've had to buy another one that's too kitschy.
I'm so desperate to get it back that I end up having to buy the next one that's too kitschy.
So, I think the first one should be more moderate.
And there's an A1 player that's easy to understand.
That's right.
I'm in a hurry for this exercise.
Five more minutes.
Oh!
Hey!
Off you go, Miru-chan!
Please push for your application time!
Yeah...
If you'd like to come on line...
Please press "apply" button!
If you like LINE, please press
Please press the issue button.
If you'd like to use the line...
What?
Please press the issue button.
If you would like to use the line, please press the
What?
I did as you said, but for 400 yen, I think it's okay.
Miryan, what did you buy for the 5th race?
I used your prediction as a reference.
Takahashi-san's prediction.
But so did I.
I don't know, but my intuition told me that 3 might be better than the exhibit.
I bought one 134, 3456 formation.
I think I was a bit dodged by the staff of the boat racing club this time. I feel like I've been dodged a little bit by the staff of the Collaborative Boat Racing Department this time.
I'm going to challenge this time with a total of 13.
I've graduated from Hitomi.
I really want to win too.
So I'm going to take on today with a total of 13.
I look forward to working with you.
It's getting deeper and deeper.
I'm getting a little tired of the name Hitomi.
Seriously?
Be confident.
I can't hit it at all.
Everyone's birthday is so special.
I don't know...
I've already lived.
I'm going to try this for five races.
I felt sorry for Hitomi's fans.
I thought I'd bought 13.
Next time, all of them.
All of them.
What if there's a tailwind?
A tailwind.
It makes it a little easier for the third store to roll in and out.
Oh, no.
And maybe a little bit of rain.
It's raining a little bit.
It's drizzling.
Rain...
When it rains, it rains.
You know...
Humidity comes out.Moisture comes out.
Engine revs a little slow.
Oh, my God.
Oh, yeah?
Oh, my God, the other one just blew up all over the place, the one I'm putting in.
Oh, my God.
I've been working on that one for a while now.
I've only been doing it with one other horse, and it's been blowing everything up.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Jinx.
Oh, no.
Oh!
Hitomi Chance
It's true.
Come here.
It'll be big!
Please!
Here we go, five races in!
How's it going?
Race start is fine.
I'm good!
He'll get away with it.
Wait! Wait! Okay!
Wait! No! No! No! No! Yes! No! No! Good! I like it!
Wait! It looks good.
My eyes someday!
What, five?
It's definitely Mirina!
I'm here too! I'm here too!I'm here too! I'm here too!
I'm here too!
But maybe it's not so good. Maybe 5 is coming.
Five is coming too fast.
It's Mirina.
There's no 5. 3?
3?
Definitely 3?
No 5.
One, three, five!
Four against three!
Four!
Come on, four!
Come on!
Four and six!
Are you sure?
They're coming, they're coming, they're coming! They're coming. They're coming. They're coming.
It's a five and a three and a five. Wow, a mini-nya box.
Wait, I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
Still three more turnstiles to go. Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Yes! Please! Number four! Number 4, please!
What should I say to cheer him up?
Let me! Let me! Four!
Four! Let me go!
Let's go! But you're losing it, aren't you?
Are we there yet? There's a lot of balls in the air. Is there a difference?Still? I'm pretty good with the ball. Pretty good, huh?
There's a difference, huh? What?
If number five doesn't miss, it's gonna be a little tough.
Wow!
Tough.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa! Wow! Whoa!
What is that?
Really, what is that?
Mummy!
Don't you understand me?
Very funny.
I'm right on formation.
That's great.
Hey!
Applause.
We've finished race five, right?
We're done.
Races one, three and five.
Miniabox.
I won!
But I also won races 1, 3 and 5.
You did it.
That's great.
Wow, wow, wow. We both won.
We won!
First time.
We did it!Yay!
By the way, how much did you both buy?
I bought 500 yen.
Oh!
How's that?
If there's a five involved, you get a payout.
300 yen.
Three hundred yen?
What, what, what, what, what, what?
What do you think?
500 yen.
That's great.
How many yen?
How much is that?
Three hundred and ninety yen.
What, what, what, what?
That's great.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
I'm not running away.
I got 500 yen.
What do you mean?
I wanna go in.
I want to go in.
No, but I was going in off the 5.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, you did it.
We did it!Yay!
That's great.
Have a good day.
I'm off.
Amazing.
Hitomi, isn't this the first time you got a refund like this?
It's a first.
First time.
First time for you and me.
I guessed it in the director's formation.
It's so cool!
Sir!
What's your favorite?
What number?
Number one.
Number two.
Number three.
Number 4
Number 5.
No.6
No.7
No.8
No. 9
No. 10
No.11
No.12
No. 13
No. 14No. 14
No. 15
No. 16
No.17
No.18
No.19
No.20
No.23
No.24
No.25
No.26
No.27
No.28
No. 29
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
That's some kind of winning wind, Navikati.
15,900 yen.
Thank you very much.
Yay!
How much did you get?
15,950 yen.
So that's how much you paid me.
About 10,000 yen.
Wow!
Crazy.
No, you can do it.
Crazy way to play...
That's right, you had to go hard now.
I had to go hard now.I'm just tickled to be able to go.
I'll take that as a yes.
I'd like to buy it in sixes.
How about six?
Some kind of gambler.
That's a casino gambler.
I was watching a youtube clip of a casino gambler.
I was watching a youtube video of a casino gambler.
I heard that you should multiply your winnings by the number of bets you win.
This is not a youtube of boat racing.
It's just a youtube of a casino.
What kind of youtube are you watching?
Well, let's put that aside.
You multiply your winnings by the amount of money you've won.
Isn't that easy?
No way.
It's like the devil whispering.
It's supposed to be lunchtime game two.
And this one.
There's A levels 1 and 4 here.
Is that what this is?
I see.
Two is one and four.
How are we looking on race six?
Race 6, we just saw the starting dots.
Number 4 is a little bit...
It's a little more aggressive than race 3.
I felt like he was going out with a gust of wind.
And yesterday's race...
I don't know...I don't know, it was a good race.
I saw a good race.
Ehhhh...
By the way, when the 4th boat
When the fourth boat went out with a gutshot, the third boat was like...
What kind of theory is it?
Oh, theory, is it?
But even if she gets out, if she closes...
We'll have no choice but to go outside.
Yes, it's like he's going to go outside.
It's like a tan mark.
It'll be like a tardy pointing.
If 4 comes in goofy...
5 or 6 is better than 3.
That's right.
The 4 boat will be able to keep up with us.
I see.
But there's a tailwind today.
She started from the fourth course.
And when you go for a turn...
I think there's a possibility that the exit will drift.
I think there's a possibility it could drift.
So, if we just look at the wind
The wind is in our favor.
The inside is stronger than the outside
It's better to go where the inside is turning first
It's safer or safer
It's safer
It's safer to go for a circle than to go long and bulge.
I'd rather go for a roundabout fingerI'd like to go for a roll-up and point.
I'd like to go for a roll-up.
Four, one, six.
Four, one, six?
As you said, 6 is the most popular.
If it's a roll, there's no 1 left.
If it were a roll-up, there'd be no 1 left.
But by rolling up.
But by rolling, the 1 can go around first.
1 can stay.
It's true that this time
It depends on whether you believe in the 1 as the head or the 4.
or believe in 4?
No way!
Hitomiji's three times.
LOL.
1441 sixes.
It's a pretty good iron plate.
Really?
I think it will be a popular one.
But after all...
Sasara just won.
Next time, let's use a strange way to call.
Very strange!
Crazy guide!
I'm so glad you're here.
It's always the first time.
I've never done this before.
I can finally play.
I can play now.You can play now.
This.
I like this one.
The engines on these 2, 3, and 5 players.
They don't look that good.
The engine of number 6 is a good engine
So
I'm sure it's a good seller.
If I buy one...
Yes, I would.
14146.
I think the payout is...
I haven't looked at the odds, but I think it's cheap.
If I were to buy at 6...
I'm going to collect the ones I'm buying.
I'll hold 3 and 5.
If 3 is the first one to hold, I'll
Wait for the 3
When I stabbed it
I was wondering if 3 could stay in the game, and
If 4 is a little bit vigorous and crushes 2 and 3
If the 5 next to it
2 is the best suited to the situation.
I thought there was a possibility that No. 5 could also stay.
I thought there was a possibility
I'll hold on to it.
Three...
Pro!
That's true, but...That's right.
It's pretty cheap.
It doesn't stick that well.
I've been able to predict a number of developments
I was able to predict a number of them in my head.
I'm sure you're right.
But it doesn't always turn out the way I imagine.
I think that Hattori, the 4th driver, is going to make the race here.
When 2 and 3 are a little depressed at the start, it's called "Kabe-cho".
In such a case, the No. 4 driver will have a hard time without a wall, so he will attack the outside with the No. 4 driver.
If that 4 takes the outside and attacks, 4-6 is totally possible.
I don't want to go crazy.
So this is not the crazy part yet.
Let's not do it once this time.
But let's definitely do it today.
Our mission
Our mission today
So I bought a rock race
I bought 135 boxes and I also bought 146 boxes.
I bought 135 boxes and also 146 boxes.
And I made a mistake. I thought it was 135, but it was 136.
But this one too...
But there might be this one, too.
I'm looking forward to it, thinking it's fate.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll be merry too.
I got a 146 box, too.
That's true.
But I'm sick of it.
I'm so scared.I'm already scared.
This race.
I'm so scared of rock races that I only buy 146 boxes anymore.
I'm already early.
Well then, I've outgrown you.
You're right, I haven't.
Why not?
No, I didn't.
You're in a funk.
I'll see you all later, Mr. Ichi.
I'm sure of it.
You're hilarious.
Just like that.
But the box...
I'm going to buy a box with everyone.
Mr. Takai...
Mr. Takai taught me a lot of things this time, too, so I guess we're similar.
That's how it goes, isn't it?
I'd like to watch Rock Deuce again, thinking it's new.
Worst.
What is it?
What? Why? Did you do that on purpose? Just now.
No. Did you just get hit?
What? I got hit?
You cheated by leaving the hit.
What?
Oh, but it's gonna come back around.
Is it going in? You think you can get in?
Let him in.
It's going in.
It's gonna go in.
It'll stretch the clothes and the athleticism.
I see. Four is good.
The corners should be better.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've never seen that pattern before.
Oh, no.
It's such-and-such African soup.
It's not Oyashiroes.
The Oyashi rose isn't growing.
It's not growing?
Does it ever grow?
It grows.
Does it basically grow?
Everyone has it, I think.
Oh, really?
If you ever have to pull out your Oyashi rose, let's do it!
Minya, you've done a great job with the Oyashi rose, let's do it!
I want to do it!
I'm sure that's the race for the crown.
That's right!
That's for sure!
I want to do it!
The wind's picking up.
It's getting windy.
Is it really going to be a strong current? This...
It's going to wash away. I'm so swept away.
Oh, what am I going to do?
Tick-tock!
I ended up buying a very ticky-tacky one!
What the hell!
It's going to increase so much!
Yes, sir!
Let the rock race begin.
What do you think?
How's it going?
Oh? Huh?
Oh! Four! Four!
Whoa! Aah! Oh, no, no, no, no! Oh, no!
Aaahhh! Aaahhh!
Four turns! Aaahhh! It's over!
I'm done! It's over!
You're done! It's over!
It's over! Don't give up!
Are you done? I only bought one. One box.
That's it, isn't it? That's it. That's it.
I buy crazy. I'm going to buy crazy.
Sashiara-san! You didn't buy it?
If you buy a Kashiko box every time, you'll end up buying a Kashiko box.
I only buy Kashiko boxes.
I see. Aaaaaaah!
Oh, my God! Is this for real?
But 3 was persistent, wasn't it?
3 and... you were trying your best, but 4 rolled over.With #3... you were trying your best, but the 4 rolled around.
Ah! Wait!
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Oh!
If I win this...
If I buy this...
If I had bought this...
But 3 and 5, which Mr. Takahashi had bought in his three-way tie, are here.
Wow! That's what I'm talking about!
So it's really amazing.
Really amazing. Really!
But I guess when the 4's are all over the place, there are no 1's left, right?
That's how it is, isn't it?
That's why there are more developments happening.
That's how it is.
4 alone!
The number 3.3...
That's what I'm talking about!
How can such a 4 come in at the top? I thought so.
But it's a solid head.
Amazing!
Nobody guessed it, did they?
Why not?
Nobody hit anything, right?
You hit it, didn't you?
Yes!
Then no one won.
Oh!
What, what, what, what?
Oh, my God!Ew!
Oh!
You're right!
Oh, my gosh!
That's amazing!
Wait, how much did you buy?
Two hundred yen.
Oh, my God!
That's amazing!
We're a team in the Equal Love Boat Race.
One team!
Even if I die alone, we're still a team!
What, you died quietly and you're still a team?
I don't see them.
Fourteen thousand.
Oh, my God!
Really?
That's 30,000 yen!
Oh, my God!
This way.
Yay!
Oh, that's great!
I'm amazed you could keep your eyes on it.
Really? I'm sure!
I'm sure.
I can't see! Make more noise!
The lady staff is making so much noise.
I noticed one thing.One thing I noticed.
I went on a trip in search of Reset Gummies.
I found them at Mega Donkey in Shibuya.
I bought it but forgot it!
Wait, I also bought Reset Gummi Lemon at Megadonki in Shibuya.
Same?
The same!
Why are you so surprised?
Shibuya Mega Donkey has Reset Gummies lemon flavor, right?
That's right!
I got mine at the Shibuya Megadonki.
I have this one... Shibuya Megadonki.
Really?
I'm the one who bought all the grapes, right?
I bought it a long time ago.
You go to Megadonki all the time.
I bought them at Megadonki in Shibuya.
I forgot. Today.
I forgot mine.
I was sure you'd bring it.
What? If I eat it, I win?
That's what I believe.
I'm just trying to reset my mind.
Like a purification.
I'm having a bad day, so I just washed my hands.
I'm just trying to cleanse myself.
That's what I mean.
I really want to brush my teeth too.
But if you washed your hands...
Suikyon.Suikyong.
I hope you're okay, Suikyon.
But Oba, yesterday...
Oba?
I was running away from the inside of
Sawada passed you.
Sawada?
He came in second.
He's usually a fast starter.
But this time, he didn't get off to a good start.
I'm not sure if he hasn't caught the start yet.
or something.
If you can see the start a little bit...
I wanted him to point a little.
Two, one...
Including Osawa, who was on tenterhooks.
Two, one, two, three...
What?
I was worried that Ober had been passed.
It didn't look good.
If he passed me, I thought it might be dangerous to fix his head.
But if he's setting good times or something...
I'd like to trust you a little.
I see.
But in your comment, Mr. Oniwa said
He beat Pella by a lot.
My legs are about normal.
He must have changed.I know you've changed.
It wasn't great.
But it seems to have gotten better.
So you've changed.
Various things.
It's huge.
Around there...
I've heard a lot of things about it.
I don't think anyone noticed.
So there it is, the column Boat Racing Channel's last race, and this is the last race.
So we're winning as a team for now, so we're doing okay.
Great... you're hiding behind the character and thinking the cash isn't so good...
I think it's finally Zenith's time.
I'm sure you'll win once you win.
I'm confident. Really? I washed my hands.
I really feel like I'm going to win.
The V's hit? The staff won? I haven't won yet.
Sorry to keep you waiting, but I'm about to win.
I'll take that one.
One, two, three on the turn.
One, two, five.
What about this one?
I think the engine of the 3rd driver, Osawa, is good.
I'm a little worried about Osawa's engine.
So, with Osawa, who has a good engine, as the core, either No.1 or No.2 will remain.
And then there is Akaba, who raced on the 6th course yesterday.
I thought his legs were about normal.
I thought that Koba, on the inside, would be more likely to roll around on the fifth course and break into the field.
So I put him in third place on course 5. I put in the third one, number 5.
I see.
I'm so happy to see the resemblance between you and me.
It makes me feel like I've won on my own.
It's like you've narrowed it down a bit from Mr. Sasahara.
Yes, that's right.
It would be cool to change it.
But I couldn't work up the courage.
I ended up buying a lot.
But I think it's good.
What happens if I win all of them?
If you win all of them, you'll win for sure.
You'll win for sure.
So it'll either be a big jump or a very ordinary one.
I don't know.
What do I do? I don't know.
I can't write it or I can't write it.
It's not a no, not at all.
I always end up with nothing at all.
Private, it doesn't matter.
If I said this is the only way to collect, I'd say it's totally fine.
What do you think?
Is today a totally perfect day?
No, but it's raining and windy.
Maybe it's a perfect day.
All day at all?
I'd like to see that, but I don't.
That's funny.
How much money do you have left?How much money do you have left, money-wise?
Including the winnings.
Okay, so you're totally fine with the winnings.
The money you just won...
I didn't spend it. I didn't spend it.
Oh?
It's over $1,000.
It's about 13,000 yen.
That's a total day's work.
It's a total day job.
Oh!
You're going to hit it!
If 123 comes in, you can cry for Mirin.
You're a winner!
The lowest price is 8x.
Eight times?
That's not good.
Well, I guess I'm out.
But what if...
What if...
You were the 39th favorite.
If something like that comes along...
It's not luck.
You'll have to pay for Mirin's last win.
Not at all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's true, we have the deposits from last time.
That's great.
Is it okay? No? Are you sure?
You're gonna win.I'm gonna get it. I'm gonna get it.
It's a really big bite.
Please hand in your mass card.
Please choose your name.
Please choose a customer's name.
You will definitely win.
Hitomi, please explain with that. My buy-in.
What?
You look embarrassed.
It's really interesting to see a girl who doesn't know anything do that.
Then, what's your buy-in?
Please tell me.
Okay. First of all, anything. All, all, all, all at one place.
Oh, so it's all in one suit.
Zen, one, three.
I see.
It's Hitomi's, zen-ichi-ii-san.
Only zen-ichi-ii-san?
And also, this is my first time to buy.
Yes. First of all, zen.
Oh.
All.
Two.
Two. Whole.
All. Two. All.
Yes, sir.
What do you think, doctor?
It's very original.
I'm having trouble with my voice. I'm having trouble with my voice.
All.
What, why, why, why, why, why, why, why?
Somehow.
I don't know anymore.
But if it's 12 or 32, I'm totally sure.
Yes. So, second place, ah, 25.
As long as all of them are in the second place, it's mine.
No, it's okay. I can do it.
I'm nervous.
What did you get?
All of it. All of it.
No, wait. This is my first time. First time I've seen you live.
It's the first time I've seen you live.
You sound like Tamori. It's the first time I've seen it live.
My 12,000 are gathered in this.
It's amazing.
Please come to the big hole. Really.
Yes, I'm sure.
That, that's the expectation, isn't it?
If it's 45, 66, and 88, we're all set.
Please, take a hit.
Please let me have it, already.
If the wind blows about 10 meters, we'll be fine.
How many meters is it blowing now?
About three or four meters.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
There's a storm brewing in five minutes.There is a storm brewing in the next five minutes from there.
Thank you for watching.
There's a comedian on my most-watched YouTube channel, Osawa-san.
He's doing a lot of boating, and he's always talking about the occult.
He's always saying that it's occult, and he's always trying to jinx it or do some kind of spell.
For example, he says that everyone should go barefoot.
I'm like, "I'm never going to see that." I'm like, "I'm never going to see that.
Sounds fun.
Let's do it once.
We'll all hold hands and never let go.
We'll never let go.
If we let go of even one hand, we're all finished
I'll never let you go, I'll never let you go, I'll never let you go.
I'll never let go
I won't let you go. I won't let you go.
You know what?
If you let go of me, I'll never let go of you. I'll never let go of you.
You're never gonna let go.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
You're only as good as the effort you put into it.
Come on, storm!
What's the height of the storm?
It's getting quieter.
I don't like it.
But you've got to put some effort into it.
Now that we've got this thing hooked up, it's going to hit us.
Don't worry.
It's going to hit! It's going to hit!
It's gonna hit! It's gonna hit!You'll be right!
7 Races
Race 7
Here we go.
Let's get you hooked up for a second, Buzz.
Five.
One team, this is...
One team.
Here we go.
Nice.
Blow the wind!
Pounding
The wind is blowing for everyone
Eh, eh, eh
What? What?
What?
eh eh eh
Boran rar
h Shilen
ni
aname
I am bad! I'm bad!
Na ahaha
Boo boo this way!
document
izar dex
Oh no, minya, minya, minya are you here?Oh, my God, Miya, oh, my God, Miya's here?
What? I mean, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I mean, it's rough. It's rough.
Rough.
They're gonna get some of this.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I'm not gonna let go of your hand. I'm not gonna let go of your hand.
I'm not gonna let go of your hand.
Twenty. Ten. Twenty thousand.
Twenty-seven thousand.
Ehh...
Ehhhh...
Eeeee...
Woah.
Eh, eh, eh, eh
This is bad.
I'm so tired.
Let go of me! I'm so tired!
Wait, wait!
I'm leaving! I'm leaving, too!
I'm leaving, too! I'm leaving!
I'm leaving, too!
Fuck!
What's the goal?
Oh, I'm on one!
Yeah!
One! What does that mean? One! What does that mean?
But I get it. But wow!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
Well, how are you two doing?
Oh, Jenny!
Jenny! Jenny!
Jenny!
I'm awesome!
I've got one too!
Jenny!
Oh, my gosh!
Yes!
Listen, I'm buying 200 yen.
Wow!
Jenny!
Oh, my gosh!
Two!
That's great!
Yeah!
Yes!
We did it!
I did it!
That's great!
It's as good as my face!
Yes!Yay!
That's great!
The three of us and I are quietly dying, and no one knows it.
I'm the only one who's dead.
I don't think they know.
But, but, but...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! I'm so happy!
Good job!
Oh, my God! He's back!
He's strong! He's back!
Yes!
We made it!
That's great!
Yay!
We're going!
Let's go!
It's not at all timely, and it's true.
You did it!
Whoo!
We did it!
The machine is here!
Huh! Oh, thank God!
We did it!
of a Yosago NO
nie er
Huh, test
Oh no!
Oh no!It's not good.
It's a good thing, but it doesn't look good.
That's great.
So, we've finished the first three races.
First, the first three races are over... and I'd like to announce the results...
Boo-hoo! 157 percent!
So, at the end... it's the first time I've ever seen this... but maybe it's because I'm a beginner...
But the more times I play, the more I think about it... and I realized that this is what it's like to be addicted to boat racing.
I'm going to ask you for a petit one...
Forty thousand!
That's 40,000 yen!
That's amazing!
Congratulations!
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad we won with the formation and in front of you!
Finally, a sense of Yes, how about you?
I'm...
Well, minus 40,000, then.
Me, the Great!
Boo boo I read it in the second part Yes Alright, I have not inspected
none man members also can go to the depths of the massachusetts in the goat of Mr. Takahashi my element is not at all hit the seven large dressing room importa
I don't have to do anything with the knowledge you've given me today, and I'm sure I'll continue to do my best.
I should continue to do my best!
She's such a goddess!
Thank you very much. I've just been through a lot of drama...
I've just been through a lot of drama, but this January, actually...
I think there's going to be an air failure.
This is the collaboration with Rosilla.
j 1I see you're going to do it at the school, in collaboration with Mr. Godzilla for the 70th anniversary.
I'm really looking forward to it. - Then I'll stay here for a week and do it.Then let's do a one-week staycation.
Let's do a week-long camp.
You're happy with that?
Yes.
For nine minutes.
In the boat racers. It was delicious.
I'll eat it too!
I'm wearing it, but I got the first part from Channel 1.
The second part is an official challenge by Boat Racer Monaka.
So, good luck with the second part, but be careful with the mega-johns.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Thank you very much for watching and please look forward to the second part.
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!